

Rae Dominique A. Angeles

Web Developer

🔀 raedominique.angeles@gmail.com 🔪 (+63) 977 812 0096

Noveleta, Cavite

PROFILE

I am a graduate of Computer Science with 3 years of experience working as a Front-End Developer in the industry where I have gained and enhanced my skills in developing user interfaces, testing, debugging, and optimizing web functionalities.

I am passionate in programming, always aiming for career advancement and professional development, hard-working in nature, great team player, I have an enthuasiastic demeanour and commitment to the things I am assigned to do. I am always willing and keen to learn more so I can continue to improve my skills, not only technical but also interpersonal.

EDUCATION

Bs Computer Science, New Era University

September 2015 - April 2019 Quezon City, Philippines

Internship - Web Developer (September 2018 -December 2018)

- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Creating Web based scoring system for the University
- Processing and creating a Client Server Request and Response
- Resolves minor bug fixes
- Creates documentation for existing developments on the projects
- Making requested changes and updates

SKILLS

HTML/Css/JavaScript | Scss | Tailwind Css React JS | Vue JS | Node JS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer, RealPage, Inc.

January 2021 – March 2023 | Pasig, Philippines

- Transforming web designs into a website.
- Maintaining the website's functionality based on client requests.
- Create and maintain software documentation
- Joined a team to develop an application for company's innovation.
- Cooperate with QA for identifying bugs before executing the application to production.

Full Stack Developer, Health Maintenance, Inc.

2020 - December 2021 | Makati, Philippines

- Created a portal for clients to view the current plan and also the history of consultations.
- Created an informative website for the company.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.
- Integrate data from various back-end services and databases.

PROJECTS

Siroter-Le-Delicieux-Cafe

March 2023 -A frontend design of a coffee shop website that allows users to determine its March 2023 information as well as look into its different services and products that the

September 2020 -

November 2020

shop offers.

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css

Movie Zone □ February 2023 -March 2023

A very informative website that allows users to browse their favorite movies as well as look its movie information.

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css

Pedal Deck 🗗 January 2022 -February 2022

A frontend design of an e-commerce website that allows user to browse and buy a bicycle of their choice.

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css

Health Maintenance, Inc Portal 🛮 November 2020 -December 2020

A Progressive Web App that allows users to view utilities/transaction history from their previous activity. Users can also view their profile as well as their dependencies.

Technologies: Vue JS, Css, Node Js and MySQL

Health Maintenance, Inc. Website

A company website that helps users know what the company is all about, who are the management team and its services. Also, the website allows users to

search their affiliated facilities and physicians.

Technologies: Vue JS, Css, Node Js and MySQL